[JENNIE KIM] LOCK ME UP AND
THROW AWAY THE KEY
HE KNOWS HOW TO GET
THE BEST OUT OF ME
I'M NO FORCE FOR THE WORLD
TO SEE
TRADE MY WHOLE LIFE
JUST TO BE
[ABEL] TELL NOBODY
I CONTROL YOU
I BROKE YOU JUST TO OWN YOU
THEY CAN'T TELL THAT
I LOVE YOU
'CAUSE YOU'RE LOYAL, BABY
I LOVE WHEN
YOU'RE SUBMISSIVE
YOU LOVE IT WHEN
I BREAK SKIN
YOU FEEL PAIN
WITHOUT FLINCHIN'
SO SAY IT
[LILY ROSE]
GIVE ME TOUGH LOVE
LEAVE ME WITH NOTHIN'
WHEN I COME DOWN
MY KIND OF LOVE
PUSH ME AND CHOKE ME
'TIL I PASS OUT
WE DON'T GOTTA
BE IN LOVE, NO
I DON'T GOTTA BE THE ONE, NO
I JUST WANNA BE ONE
OF YOUR GIRLS TONIGHT
WE DON'T GOTTA BE
IN LOVE, NO
I DON'T GOTTA BE THE ONE, NO
I JUST WANNA BE ONE
OF YOUR GIRLS TONIGHT, OH
PUSH ME DOWN, HOLD ME DOWN
SPIT IN MY MOUTH
WHILE YOU TURN ME OUT
I WANNA TAKE YOUR
LIGHT INSIDE
TEAR ME DOWN, SNUFF ME OUT
HANDS ON MY NECK
WHILE YOU PUSH IT UP
AND I'M SCREAMIN' NOW
[ABEL] GIVE ME TOUGH LOVE
LEAVE ME WITH NOTHIN'
WHEN I COME DOWN
MY KIND OF LOVE
FORCE ME AND CHOKE ME
'TIL I PASS OUT
[LILY ROSE] WE DON'T GOTTA BE
IN LOVE, NO
I DON'T GOTTA BE THE ONE, NO
I JUST WANNA BE ONE OF YOUR
GIRLS TONIGHT (TONIGHT)
WE DON'T GOTTA BE
IN LOVE, NO
I DON'T GOTTA BE THE ONE,
NO (OH)
I JUST WANNA BE ONE
OF YOUR GIRLS TONIGHT, OH
[JENNIE KIM] LOCK ME UP AND
THROW AWAY THE KEY
HE KNOWS HOW TO GET
THE BEST OUT OF ME
I'M NO FORCE FOR THE WORLD
TO SEE
TRADE MY WHOLE LIFE
JUST TO BE
TOP OF THE WORLD,
BUT I'M STILL NOT FREE
THIS IS A SECRET THAT I KEEP
UNTIL IT'S GONE, I CAN
NEVER FIND PEACE
WASTE MY WHOLE LIFE
JUST TO BE
[LILY ROSE] WE DON'T GOTTA BE
IN LOVE, NO
I DON'T GOTTA BE THE ONE, NO
I JUST WANNA BE ONE OF YOUR
GIRLS TONIGHT (TONIGHT)
WE DON'T GOTTA BE
IN LOVE, NO
I DON'T GOTTA BE THE ONE,
NO (OH)
I JUST WANNA BE ONE OF YOUR
GIRLS TONIGHT (OH), OH